{
  "meta": {
    "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
    "perDifficulty": 20,
    "createdAt": "2026-01-17T09:57:32.275375"
  },
  "problems": {
    "1": [
      {
        "id": "P9330239337833078",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 89°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1372729548009229",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 89°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2424580384102868",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 81°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2256716462816638",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 155°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "둔각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0524911068394627",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 79°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P3302936234873388",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 125°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "둔각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1005449047773479",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 140°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "둔각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0051814464071300",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 55°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9779107118330872",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 160°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "둔각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4069074515468834",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 60°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4774485204408965",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 141°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "둔각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7559110594087395",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 71°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P3211677021191667",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 93°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "둔각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9079369587356224",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 35°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P6522987304190796",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 42°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5351522768936047",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 79°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9132297256698524",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 29°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4178849822450053",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 64°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9339226105782002",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 65°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9971718030885100",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "각의 크기가 29°일 때 예각/직각/둔각 중 무엇인가?",
        "answer": "예각",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      }
    ],
    "2": [
      {
        "id": "P1863116319224889",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "111°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "69",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0092671684800997",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "84°의 여각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "6",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9284548460170172",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "155°의 여각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "-65",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4543490781567950",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "95°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "85",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P8892599637699165",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "149°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "31",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2728370814979924",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "44°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "136",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1624942625397386",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "38°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "142",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7185981734558871",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "127°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "53",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7907676644252557",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "13°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "167",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1754949138384647",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "155°의 여각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "-65",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5152806589597959",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "113°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "67",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P6692558534099542",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "32°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "148",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4774540984898930",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "57°의 여각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "33",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2607852770654438",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "73°의 여각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "17",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7537566517814570",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "70°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "110",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5824607515549848",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "94°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "86",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2615531508153927",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "156°의 여각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "-66",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0621243318005361",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "102°의 여각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "-12",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P3068063420036198",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "40°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "140",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P6902903774188142",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "113°의 보각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "67",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      }
    ],
    "3": [
      {
        "id": "P3675439031021702",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2191286009353439",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "평각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "180",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4781818997352240",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "평각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "180",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7477348371508565",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4158456154312246",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7573505233043260",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7618596199711071",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "평각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "180",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5255066562201677",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "평각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "180",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0781027221474401",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0617580475566837",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "평각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "180",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5727016742278647",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "평각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "180",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1645371565827550",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "평각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "180",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1162400221846642",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7169179661806500",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "평각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "180",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0909416444516878",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P8086920831772372",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1319443398210990",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4567984757118760",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5587971989987663",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "평각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "180",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7232800798250023",
        "unitId": "m1-1-2-I-1",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "한 바퀴각의 크기는?",
        "answer": "360",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "°",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      }
    ]
  }
}